<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SimpleNewsLocal-IOT</string>
    <string name="title_one">5 Tips Every Android Developer Should Know</string>
    <string name="description_one">Starting Android Development is easy, but having some tips is always better. I wrote some tips in this post to help you make your Android Development journey more better. These 5 tips every Android Developer should know</string>

    <string name="title_two">Why we should use Android Bundle for value-passing instead of Intent?</string>
    <string name="description_two">According to common usage, developers prefer to pass data with Intent, but there is better and less code way to pass data between Activities by using Bundle in Android</string>

    <string name="title_three">Android App Coding Best Practices | 10 Points</string>
    <string name="description_three">1. Choose Naming Convention Wisely
The idea is that “code should explain itself”
Naming Convention is the first thing comes into my mind when creating any file and also plays an important role in long term maintenance of a project, So if used properly it reduce the effort needed to read and understand source code.</string>

    <string name="title_four">Paging3 — Doing Recyclerview Pagination the Right Way</string>
    <string name="description_four">Jetpack Paging library release version 3.0.0-alpha03 is full of new features and is Kotlin first with a pinch of Coroutines &amp; Flow 😊.</string>

    <string name="title_five">Android memory leaks by Programmer’s mistake</string>
    <string name="description_five">When we develop android apps we often encounter memory leaks and If we don’t know what is memory leak and how to handle this, then it becomes a very tedious task to handle.</string>

    <string name="title_six">Don’t abuse Kotlin’s scope functions</string>
    <string name="description_six">Scope functions
Kotlin’s standard library contains several functions whose sole purpose is to execute a block of code within the context of an object.
When you call such a function on an object with a lambda expression provided, it forms a temporary scope.</string>

    <string name="title_seven">Enhance your android App with Custom View</string>
    <string name="description_seven">When you start the android development, you are discovering the many UI components already existing in the Android SDK (TextView, Layout, ImageView, … ).</string>

    <string name="title_eight">Coroutines in Just 5 Minutes | Complete Android Coroutine Best Practices</string>
    <string name="description_eight">“The beautiful thing about learning is that nobody can take it away from you.” — B.B. King</string>

    <string name="title_nine">RecyclerView in a better exhaustive way (Kotlin only)</string>
    <string name="description_nine">The UiModel has an id that represents its uniqueness, title will be using on both header and title type whereas the description only uses in the ITEM_TYPE type.</string>

    <string name="title_ten">Kotlin: Sealed Classes for better handling of API Response</string>
    <string name="description_ten">While working in Java to represent a fixed set of constants, a classic choice was to use an enum. An enum type is a special data type that enables a variable to be a set of predefined constants. The variable must be equal to one of the values that have been predefined for it.</string>
</resources>